>>i: What would you want to tell someone how
is not from Texas about yourself, your family
or your community?
>>s: About myself...well no...not about myself.
No, but uhm...El Paso is a really nice place
to come and visit, to stay, to live. The weather's
great, it's very hot, pero it’s better than
having tornados and tsunamis and all of that.
I would say it's great over here, because
we have ah...pues Mexico right there, so we
have enchiladas, tacos, you know. I think
El Paso is very Mexican. So it's a great place
to, to live.
>>i: ¿Tienes platillos mexicanos favoritos?
>>s: ¡Ay, sí! Los chiles rellenos, I love
chiles rellenos, no más que, I don't know
how to eat hot chile, por eso me dicen mis hijos: tú
no eres Mexican, mom. Pero I love chile rellenos,
yeah.
>>i: Qué rico. Bueno, Norma, muchas gracias
por la entrevista.
>>s: Thank you.
>>i: Hasta luego.
>>s: Okay.