>> i: ¿Y tu te consideras mexicana, mexicana-americana,
texana, americana?
>> s: I would say Mexican-American. Solamente
porque nací aquí es ... o sea siempre he
vivido aquí y así pero... I mean, I'm ... I
don't, like ... I'm not one of those people
that says, like, 'Oh, you know, I don't wanna
be a Mexican' or anything. Like, I like ... I
like my Mexican culture a lot. But, I mean,
I've lived here all my life so I can't say
I'm Mexican when I really never even lived
over there. I would want to, though. Me ... me
gustaria vivir allá nomás para ir a caminar
al centro. [Risa]
>> i: ¿Y dónde irias a vivir en Mexico,
a que parte? [Pausa]
>> s: Al ... ¿Cómo se... The ... how do
you say... ¿Distrito Federal?
>> i: Uh-huh. Distrito Federal. ¿Mexico D.F.?
>> s: Sí.
>> i: Mexico City.
>> s: Quiero ... quiero ir allí para ir a
visitar el ... la ciudad porque me ... me
han dicho que es ... que es bien bonito allí.
Y quiero llevar a mi mamá.
>> i: Impresionante.
>> s: Sí.
>> i: Sí.
>> s: Have you [inaudible] ...
>> i: Sí, yo hay ido.
>> s: I really wanna go. I've heard about
the churches and the museums. One day.