>> i: Wow. Okay. ¿Y te mudarías a otro estado
en Estados Unidos? ¿A California?
>> s: California, sí.
>> i: ¿A Chicago?
>> s: No. Ya para allá, no.
>> i: ¿No?
>> s: No. I've ... es que no ...
>> i: ¿A Florida?
>> s: A Florida, sí. I think more, like,
over there, like, on the East Coast would
be too much of a drastic change for me because,
I mean, there's no Mexican people over there.
I feel so out of place.
>> i: ¿O no tantos?
>> s: Pues, sí. Yeah. Yeah, there's not a
lot over there, and I'm ... I'm kind of, like,
you know, 'What if they're mean to me and
stuff?' I think that [inaudible].
>> i: Yeah. ¿Y has experimentado una vez
una discriminación?
>> s: No. Pero mirada, sí...mirada, sí.
>> i: ¿Cómo qué? ¿Cómo te sientes?
>> s: Like... I don't know. Like, it's weird.
Like, you know, like, they just look at you,
like ... like, 'Oh.' Like, 'Ugh.' I'm just,
like, What ... 'What am I doing?' Yeah. But,
I mean, it's a little sad, I guess, I would
say. But that's it.